(upbeat music)
(singer vocalizing)
♪ Last Christmas I gave you my heart ♪
♪ But the very next day you gave it away ♪
♪ This year, to save me from tears ♪
♪ I'll give it to someone special ♪
♪ Last Christmas I gave you my heart ♪
♪ But the very next day you gave it away ♪
♪ You gave it away ♪
♪ This year, to save me from tears ♪
♪ I'll give it to someone special ♪
♪ Special ♪
♪ Once bitten and twice shy ♪
♪ I keep my distance, but
you still catch my eye ♪
♪ Tell me baby, do you recognize me ♪
♪ Well, it's been a year,
it doesn't surprise me ♪
♪ Happy Christmas, I
wrapped it up and sent it ♪
♪ With a note saying, "I
love you," I meant it ♪
♪ Now I know what a fool I've been ♪
♪ But if you kissed me now,
I know you'd fool me again ♪
♪ Last Christmas I gave you my heart ♪
♪ But the very next day you gave it away ♪
♪ You gave it away ♪
♪ This year, to save me from tears ♪
♪ I'll give it to someone special ♪
♪ Special ♪
♪ Last Christmas I gave you my heart ♪
♪ But the very next day you gave it away ♪
♪ This year, to save me from tears ♪
♪ I'll give it to someone special ♪
♪ Special ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, baby ♪
♪ A crowded room,
friends with tired eyes ♪
♪ I'm hiding from you
and your soul of ice ♪
♪ My God, I thought you
were someone to rely on ♪
♪ Me? I guess I was a shoulder to cry on ♪
♪ A face on a lover with
a fire in his heart ♪
♪ A man under cover,
but you tore me apart ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, now I've found a real love ♪
♪ You'll never fool me again ♪
♪ Last Christmas I gave you my heart ♪
♪ But the very next day you gave it away ♪
♪ You gave it away ♪
♪ This year, to save me from tears ♪
♪ I'll give it to someone special ♪
♪ Special ♪
♪ Last Christmas I gave you my heart ♪
♪ But the very next day you gave it away ♪
♪ You gave me away ♪
♪ This year, to save me from tears ♪
♪ I'll give it to someone special ♪
♪ Special ♪
♪ A face on a lover with
a fire in his heart ♪
♪ I gave you mine ♪
♪ A man under cover but
you tore him apart ♪
♪ Maybe next year I'll
give it to someone ♪
♪ I'll give it to someone special ♪
♪ Special ♪
♪ So long ♪